http://www.eduplace.com/forums/html/terms.html

Terms and Conditions of Use
By using the Web pages hosted by Houghton Mifflin Company and/or its various divisions and subsidiaries (collectively referred to as “HMCo”), you agree to the following terms and conditions:
The materials posted on these pages by HMCo may be retrieved solely for your own personal use and may be downloaded to your own hard disk or sent to a printer solely for that purpose. You may not otherwise copy, modify or distribute the contents of these pages without the express permission of HMCo.
Portions of these pages provide users an opportunity to exchange ideas and information.
The ideas and information posted do not necessarily reflect the views of HMCo.
While using these pages, you may not post, transmit, or otherwise distribute any material that may be unlawful, obscene, defamatory, threatening, infringing on any copyright or other rights of others, or damaging to software or hardware.
You may not advertise or solicit on these pages without HMCo's express permission.
HMCo reserves the right, which it may or may not exercise, to review, edit or delete any material that it deems to be inappropriate or in violation of these Terms and Conditions of Use. NOTWITHSTANDING THE ABOVE, HMCO EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY MATERIAL COMMUNICATED BY THIRD PARTIES THROUGH THESE PAGES OR FOR ANY CLAIMS, DAMAGES OR LOSSES RESULTING FROM THE USE THEREOF.
By posting or submitting material to these pages you represent that you have all necessary rights in and to such material and that such material will not infringe on any personal or proprietary rights of any third parties.
You authorize HMCo to use and/or authorize others to use such material in any manner or medium.
You may obtain access to other sites on the Internet through these pages.
By providing this service HMCo is not undertaking any responsibility or liability for information or publications of third parties on the Internet even if you access them through these pages.
HMCO MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THESE PAGES OR THEIR CONTENTS (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION MATERIAL COMMUNICATED BY THIRD PARTIES), WHICH ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS.
HMCO DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WITH RESPECT TO THESE PAGES.
HMCO MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY THESE PAGES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE PAGES OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THEM AVAILABLE ARE FREE FROM VIRUSES, WORMS OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
HMCO ALSO MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO WHETHER THE INFORMATION
ACCESSIBLE VIA THESE PAGES IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT.
IN NO EVENT SHALL HMCO, ITS EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS, OR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION, OR DELIVERY OF THESE PAGES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SUCH AS, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF ANTICIPATED PROFITS, BENEFITS, USE, OR DATA RESULTING FROM THE USE OF THESE PAGES.
These pages are controlled and operated by HMCo in the United States and are intended for use within the United States. HMCo makes no representation that materials on these pages are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access these pages from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws. These Terms and Conditions of Use shall be construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Any action to enforce these Terms and Conditions of Use shall be brought in the federal or state courts located in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.
HMCo reserves the right to change these Terms and Conditions of Use at any time without notice.
Privacy Information
Houghton Mifflin Company recognizes the importance of protecting the information that we collect from customers during the process of registering for a service, product, newsletter,or membership area of a Houghton Mifflin Company site. It is our policy to use the information we acquire through
the registration process or through user postings at our sites for internal business uses only, and we maintain appropriate security measures to keep this information private. Gathering this information helps us develop Web sites and products to match your interests.
You should be aware that personal information--such as your name or e-mail address--that you voluntarily disclose on bulletin boards or in chat areas that are accessible to other users could be collected and disclosed by others. Houghton Mifflin Company cannot take any responsibility for such collection or disclosure.
Occasionally, Houghton Mifflin uses “cookies” to store pertinent user information during a session. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a designated file on your computer. Houghton Mifflin only uses cookies for the purpose of holding information during online sessions (for example, to hold answers to online quizzes for short-term storage, or to create a temporary
ID for use in a multiple-session assessment).
If you have any questions about the Houghton Mifflin privacy statement, contact Chris Hogg, Director, Internet and Web Development, at (617) 351-3739.
Children's On-line Privacy Information
The following paragraphs summarize Houghton Mifflin's policy regarding the collection and use of personal information about children.
Types of personal information collected: Under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, “personal information” is defined as individually identifiable information such as a first and last name, a home or other physical address including street name and city or town, an e-mail address, a telephone number, a Social Security number, or persistent identifiers such as customer or processor serial numbers held in a cookie, where the identifier is associated with individually identifiable information. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a designated file on a user's computer. Houghton Mifflin usually does not collect personal information, as defined under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We collect and use only as much information about children as necessary for the activity, and do not condition participation in any on-line activity on the disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary. Occasionally, we use cookies to store pertinent user information during a session.
Use of personal information: We use the information we collect from children only for internal business purposes, and/or to give credit to children for work they have created. We contact children by e-mail only in response to their requests for information or assistance. Houghton Mifflin uses cookies solely for the purpose of holding information during on-line sessions (for example, to hold answers to on-line quizzes for short-term storage, or to create an ID for use in a multiple-session assessment). If, however, a child voluntarily discloses personal information--such as a name or e-mail address--on bulletin boards or in chat areas that are accessible to other users, then such information could be collected and disclosed by others. Houghton Mifflin cannot take any responsibility for such collection or disclosure.
Involvement of parents: In accordance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Act, we will notify parents when collecting personal information from children, and will seek parental consent before collecting, using and/or disclosing certain personal information from children. A parent may review and have deleted their child's personal information, and may refuse to permit further collection or use of their child's information by contacting the Houghton Mifflin representatives listed below. Parents may consent to our collection and use of their child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to others.
How to get in touch with Houghton Mifflin: The following list has the names, addresses, and phone numbers of the individuals operating Web sites for the various divisions and subsidiaries of Houghton Mifflin Company. If you would like to ask who to talk to for a particular question, please contact Chris Hogg, Internet and Web Development.
Division: Corporate IT
Name: Chris Hogg
Title: Director, Internet and Web Development
Address: 222 Berkeley Street, 5th Floor
Boston, Massachusetts 02116-3764
Telephone Number: (617)-351-3699
Email Address: Chris_Hogg@hmco.com
Division: School
Address: 1560 Sherman Avenue
Evanston,
Illinois 60201
Telephone Number: (847)-869-2300, ext. 3161
Email Address: Susan_Shorey@hmco.com
Division: McDougal Littell
Name: Sue Cowden
Title: Vice President, Director of Marketing and
Technology
Address: 1560 Sherman Avenue
Evanston, Illinois 60201
Telephone Number: (847)-869-2300 , ext. 3817
Email Address:
Susan_Cowden@hmco.com
Division: Great Source Education Group
Name: Lauren McDonough
Title: Director of Web Initiatives
Address: 181 Ballardvale Street
Wilmington, MA 01887
Telephone Number: 978-661-1489
E-mail Address: lauren_mcdonough@hmco.com
Email Address: trade_webmaster@hmco.com
If you do not agree with these Terms and Conditions of Use, do not use the Web pages hosted by HMCo.
Great Source Education Group, Inc., McDougal Littell Inc., and The Riverside Publishing Company are wholly owned subsidiaries of Houghton Mifflin Company.
Use the Back button on your Web browser to return to the previous page.
Education Place
Site Index
Copyright © 1998-2004 Houghton Mifflin Company. All rights reserved.
